{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Нигерия",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Flag_of_Nigeria.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Кения",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/Flag_of_Kenya.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Конго",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Flag_of_the_Democratic_Republic_of_the_Congo.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Мали",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/92/Flag_of_Mali.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Кот-д'Ивуар",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/Flag_of_C%C3%B4te_d%27Ivoire.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Кабо-Верде",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Flag_of_Cape_Verde.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Зимбабве",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6a/Flag_of_Zimbabwe.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Фиджи",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Flag_of_Fiji.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Папуа-Новая Гвинея",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Flag_of_Papua_New_Guinea.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Французская Полинезия",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/db/Flag_of_French_Polynesia.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Перу",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/Flag_of_Peru_%28state%29.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Колумбия",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Flag_of_Colombia.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Кюрасао",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Flag_of_Cura%C3%A7ao.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Гайана",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/99/Flag_of_Guyana.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Соломоновы острова",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Flag_of_the_Solomon_Islands.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Андорра",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Flag_of_Andorra.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Мальта",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/73/Flag_of_Malta.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Ватикан",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Flag_of_the_Vatican_City_%282023%E2%80%93present%29.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Словения",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/Flag_of_Slovenia.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Албания",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Flag_of_Albania.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Северная Македония",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Flag_of_North_Macedonia.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Босния и Герцеговина",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bf/Flag_of_Bosnia_and_Herzegovina.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Сан-Марино",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Flag_of_San_Marino.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Саудовская Аравия",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Flag_of_Saudi_Arabia.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Боливия",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Bandera_de_Bolivia_%28Estado%29.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Непал",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9b/Flag_of_Nepal.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Афганистан",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Flag_of_the_Taliban.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Черногория",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Flag_of_Montenegro.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Оман",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Flag_of_Oman.svg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Флаг какой страны изображен? ",
            "correctAnswer": "Бахрейн",
            "flag": "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Flag_of_Bahrain.svg"
        }
    ],
    "countries": [
        "Андорра",
        "Мальта",
        "Ватикан",
        "Словения",
        "Албания",
        "Северная Македония",
        "Босния и Герцеговина",
        "Сан-Марино",
        "Эстония",
        "Португалия",
        "Россия",
        "Болгария",
        "Черногория",
        "Германия",
        "Ирландия",
        "Бахрейн",
        "Оман",
        "Афганистан",
        "Непал",
        "Боливия",
        "Саудовская Аравия",
        "Соломоновы острова",
        "Гайана",
        "Кюрасао",
        "Колумбия",
        "Перу",
        "Французская Полинезия",
        "Папуа-Новая Гвинея",
        "Фиджи",
        "Зимбабве",
        "Кабо-Верде",
        "Кот-д'Ивуар",
        "Мали",
        "Конго",
        "Кения",
        "Нигерия"
    ]
}